{
    "subject": "resource/Sam_Kinison",
    "predicate": "ontology/genre",
    "object": "resource/Observational_comedy",
    "human_readable": "Sam Kinison's genre is Observational comedy.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9127907156944275,
            "question": "What made Sam Kinison's Observational comedy unique?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8753412365913391,
            "question": "What genre does Sam Kinison's comedy belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8501585721969604,
            "question": "What type of comedy is Sam Kinison known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7439757585525513,
            "question": "Can you describe the style of humor used by Sam Kinison?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.719561755657196,
            "question": "Is Observational comedy a popular genre today?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6960088610649109,
            "question": "How did Sam Kinison's comedic style influence other comedians?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6333343386650085,
            "question": "What are some common themes explored in Observational comedy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5790589451789856,
            "question": "What is a defining characteristic of Observational comedy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5606105923652649,
            "question": "Are there any other comedians known for Observational comedy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.391845703125,
            "question": "Can you give examples of jokes commonly found in Observational comedy?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Sam Kinison's genre is Observational comedy.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4363_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any other comedians known for Observational comedy?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4363_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is a defining characteristic of Observational comedy?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4363_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some common themes explored in Observational comedy?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4363_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4363_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4363_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4363_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4363_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4363_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4363_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4363_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4363_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4363_89.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4363_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. The documents describe Sam Kinison as a stand-up comedian and actor, and his comedy style is characterized as crass observational humor, especially towards women and dating. This suggests that his genre is indeed Observational comedy."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement that Sam Kinison's comedy was observational humor, particularly focused on women and dating. Therefore, it can be inferred that his genre is observational comedy."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}